<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dye on Spices &amp; Spice Terminology Database ⸙</title>
    <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/categories/dye/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dye on Spices &amp; Spice Terminology Database ⸙</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://partigabor.github.io/spice/categories/dye/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Saffron</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/saffron/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/saffron/</guid>
      <description>Saffron#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian saffron زعفران 藏紅花 sáfrány Saffron (Crocus sativus L.) is a culinary spice and dye from the Iridaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Greece.2 It is used for its stigma (style), primarily for bouillabaise, rice; fevers. Its aroma is described as pungent, bitter, with a heat index of 0.3
Overview#id saffron species name Crocus sativus L. family Iridaceae part used stigma (style) macroarea Med region of origin Greece cultivation Iran; Spain; Kashmir; etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turmeric</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/turmeric/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/turmeric/</guid>
      <description>Turmeric#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian turmeric كركم 薑黃 kurkuma Turmeric (Curcuma longa L.) is a culinary and medicinal and ritualistic spice and dye from the Zingiberaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of India.2 It is used for its rhizome, primarily for curries, dye; antiseptic. Its aroma is described as warm, acrid, bitter, with a heat index of 3.3
Overview#id turmeric species name Curcuma longa L. family Zingiberaceae part used rhizome macroarea Asia region of origin India cultivation China; Honduras; India; Indonesia; Jamaica color orange-yellow botanical database POWO Names#English#term source Indian saffron OED curcuma OED turmeric OED Arabic#script term literal source أصابع صفر aṣābiʿ ṣufr yellow fingers Wikipedia عقدة صفراء ʿuqda ṣafrā&#39; yellow knob Baalbaki, 1995 عروق صفر ʿurūq ṣufr yellow roots Amar, 2017 زعفران هندي zaʿfarān hindī Indian saffron Amar, 2017 شجرة الخطاطيف shajarat al-khaṭāṭīf tree of hooks Amar, 2017 هرد hurd lane_arabic-english_1863 كركم kurkum Wehr, 1976 Chinese#script term literal source 黃薑 huángjiāng yellow-ginger Defrancis, 2003 薑黃 jiānghuáng ginger-yellow Kleeman, 2010 鬱金 yùjīn yü-gold Schafer, 1985 POWO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
