<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>herb on Spices &amp; Spice Terminology Database 1.0 (Beta)</title>
    <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/categories/herb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in herb on Spices &amp; Spice Terminology Database 1.0 (Beta)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://partigabor.github.io/spice/categories/herb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coriander</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/materials/coriander/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/materials/coriander/</guid>
      <description>Coriander#Illustration of Coriandrum sativum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887)Coriander (Coriandrum sativum L.) is a culinary spice and herb from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Mediterranean; W. Asia; India; SW As.2 It is used for its fruit and leaf, primarily for curries; anti-microbial. Its aroma is described as warm, aromatic, sweet, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian coriander كزبرة 芫荽 koriander Overview#id coriander species name Coriandrum sativum L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dill</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/materials/dill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/materials/dill/</guid>
      <description>Dill#Illustration of Anethum graveolens L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887)Dill (Anethum graveolens L.) is a culinary spice and herb from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Nort Africa; West Asia.2 It is used for its fruit and leaf, primarily for pickles, fish, breads; gripe. Its aroma is described as bitter-sweet, cool, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian dill شبت 蒔蘿 kapor Overview#id dill species name Anethum graveolens L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fennel</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/materials/fennel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/materials/fennel/</guid>
      <description>Fennel#Illustration of Foeniculum vulgare Mill. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887)Fennel (Foeniculum vulgare Mill.) is a culinary spice and herb and vegetable from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Med.2 It is used for its fruit and leaf, primarily for fish, breads, sausages; colic. Its aroma is described as licorice-like, warm, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian fennel شمر 茴香 édeskömény Overview#id fennel species name Foeniculum vulgare Mill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fenugreek</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/materials/fenugreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/materials/fenugreek/</guid>
      <description>Fenugreek#Illustration of Trigonella foenum-graecum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887)Fenugreek (Trigonella foenum-graecum L.) is a culinary spice and herb from the Fabaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of S Eur; W As.2 It is used for its seed and leaf, primarily for curries, breads; diabetes. Its aroma is described as like burnt sugar, bitter, with a heat index of 2.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian fenugreek حلبة 胡蘆巴 görögszéna Overview#id fenugreek species name Trigonella foenum-graecum L.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
