<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Spices &amp; Spice Terminology Database</title>
    <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Spices &amp; Spice Terminology Database</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright</copyright><atom:link href="https://partigabor.github.io/spice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Allspice</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/allspice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/allspice/</guid>
      <description>Allspice#Overview#id allspice species Pimenta dioica (L.) Merr. family Myrtaceae plant part used unripe fruit; leaf region of origin S. Mexico to C. America; Caribbean macroarea Americas cultivation Jamaica, Mexico color dark brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian allspice; pimento; Jamaica pepper فلفل إفرنجي fulful ifranjī [European pepper] 多香果 duōxiāngguǒ [many-spice-fruit] szegfűbors [clove-pepper] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anise</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/anise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/anise/</guid>
      <description>Anise#Overview#id anise species Pimpinella anisum L. family Apiaceae/Umbelliferae plant part used fruit; oil region of origin E. Mediterranean; W. Asia macroarea E. Med. cultivation Turkey, Egypt, Spain, Russia, Italy, etc. color light brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian anise; aniseed nan 茴芹 huíqín [anise-celery] nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asafoetida</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/asafoetida/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/asafoetida/</guid>
      <description>Asafoetida#Overview#id asafoetida species Ferula foetida (Bunge) Regel family Apiaceae/Umbelliferae plant part used gum-resin (latex) region of origin Iran; W. and C. Asia macroarea Asia cultivation Iran; Afghanistan color from pale yellow to brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian asafoetida; hing; devil&amp;rsquo;s dung nan nan ördöggyökér [devil&amp;rsquo;s root] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caraway</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/caraway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/caraway/</guid>
      <description>Caraway#Overview#id caraway species Carum carvi L. family Apiaceae/Umbelliferae plant part used fruit region of origin Mediterranean; Eurasia macroarea Eurasia cultivation Denmark, Lebanon, The Netherlands, Poland color dark brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan nan **fűszerkömény ** [spice-cumin] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardamom</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/cardamom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/cardamom/</guid>
      <description>Cardamom#Overview#id cardamom species Elettaria cardamomum (L.) Maton family Zingiberaceae plant part used fruit (seed pods, capsules) region of origin India macroarea Asia cultivation Guatemala; India; Sri Lanka; Tanzania; Papua New Guinea color green seed pods, brown seeds link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan 荳蔻/豆蔻 dòukòu [bean-cardamom] nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cassia</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/cassia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/cassia/</guid>
      <description>Cassia#Overview#id cassia species Cinnamomum cassia (L.) J.Presl. family Lauraceae plant part used bark; fruit region of origin Southeast China macroarea Asia cultivation Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Timor-Leste; etc. color reddish brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan سليخة salīkha [peel; bark] 肉桂 ròuguì [flesh-cinnamon] kasszia(fahéj) [cassia (tree-bark)] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chile</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/chile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/chile/</guid>
      <description>Chile#Overview#id chile species Capsicum annuum L. family Solanaceae plant part used fruit region of origin Central America macroarea Americas cultivation Ethiopia, India, Kenya, Mexico, Nigeria, Pakistan, Tanzania, etc. color red and green in many shades link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan فلفل حار fulful hārr [hot pepper] 辣椒 làjiāo [pungent-pepper] nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinnamon</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/cinnamon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/cinnamon/</guid>
      <description>Cinnamon#Overview#id cinnamon species Cinnamomum verum J.Presl. family Lauraceae plant part used bark; leaf region of origin Sri Lanka; SW. India macroarea Asia cultivation Sri Lanka; Seychelles; Madagascar; India color warm yellowish-brown, cinnamon \sample{cinnamon} link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan قرفة qirfa [rind; bark] 錫蘭肉桂 xīlánròuguì [Ceylon-flesh-cinnamon] fahéj [tree-bark] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clove</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/clove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/clove/</guid>
      <description>Clove#Overview#id clove species Syzygium aromaticum (L.) Merr. &amp;amp; L.M.Perry family Myrtaceae plant part used flower buds region of origin Moluccas (Indonesia) macroarea Asia cultivation Indonesia, Malaysia, Tanzania color rich, reddish brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan 丁香 dīngxiāng [nail-spice] szegfűszeg [nail-grass-nail] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coriander</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/coriander/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/coriander/</guid>
      <description>Coriander#Overview#id coriander species Coriandrum sativum L. family Apiaceae/Umbelliferae plant part used fruit; leaf region of origin Mediterranean; W. Asia; India macroarea Asia cultivation Argentina, India, Morocco, Romania, Spain, Yugoslavia color light yellow link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian coriander; cilantro; Chinese parsley nan 芫荽 yán​sui [lilac-coriander] nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cumin</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/cumin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/cumin/</guid>
      <description>Cumin#Overview#id cumin species Cuminum cyminum L. family Apiaceae/Umbelliferae plant part used fruit region of origin W. &amp;amp; C. Asia; India macroarea Asia cultivation India, Iran, Lebanon color light brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan nan római kömény [Roman cumin] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dill</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/dill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/dill/</guid>
      <description>Dill#Overview#id dill species Anethum graveolens L. family Apiaceae/Umbelliferae plant part used fruit; leaf region of origin Nort Africa; West Asia macroarea Med.; W. Asia cultivation India color greyish brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan nan nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fennel</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/fennel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/fennel/</guid>
      <description>Fennel#Overview#id fennel species Foeniculum vulgare Mill. family Apiaceae/Umbelliferae plant part used fruit; leaf region of origin Mediterranean; W. Asia; India macroarea Med.; W. Asia cultivation Argentina, Bulgaria, Germany, Greece, India, Lebanon color light green to light brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan 茴香 huíxiāng [hui-spice] édeskömény [sweet-cumin] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fenugreek</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/fenugreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/fenugreek/</guid>
      <description>Fenugreek#Overview#id fenugreek species Trigonella foenum-graecum L. family Fabaceae/Leguminosae plant part used seed; leaf region of origin W. Asia macroarea Asia cultivation India color mustard yellow seeds link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan nan görögszéna [greek-hay] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginger</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/ginger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/ginger/</guid>
      <description>Ginger#Overview#id ginger species Zingiber officinale Roscoe family Zingiberaceae plant part used rhizome region of origin South East Asia; India (secondary) macroarea Asia cultivation India, Jamaica, Nigeria, Sierra Leone color light yellow when fresh, beige when powdered link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan nan nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Pepper</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/long_pepper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/long_pepper/</guid>
      <description>Long Pepper#Overview#id long pepper species Piper longum L. family Piperaceae plant part used fruit region of origin E. Himalaya to S. China; Indo-China macroarea Asia cultivation India, Indonesia, Thailand color dreen to red when ripe, dark brown when dried link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan nan hosszú bors [long-pepper] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mace</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/mace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/mace/</guid>
      <description>Mace#Overview#id mace species Myristica fragrans Houtt. family Myristicaceae plant part used aril region of origin Moluccas (Indonesia) macroarea Asia cultivation Grenada, Indonesia color crimson red aril whn fresh, pale yellow when dried link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan 肉豆蔻皮 ròudòukòupí [flesh-bean-cardamom-skin] szerecsendió-virág [Saracen nut flower] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutmeg</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/nutmeg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/nutmeg/</guid>
      <description>Nutmeg#Overview#id nutmeg species Myristica fragrans Houtt. family Myristicaceae plant part used seed region of origin Moluccas (Indonesia) macroarea Asia cultivation Grenada, Indonesia color pale brown nut, dark when powdered link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan جوز الطيب jawz al-ṭīb [fragrant nut] 肉豆蔻 ròudòukòu [flesh-bean-cardamom] szerecsendió [Saracen nut] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepper</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/pepper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/pepper/</guid>
      <description>Pepper#Overview#id pepper species Piper nigrum L. family Piperaceae plant part used fruit region of origin Malabar coast (South India) macroarea Asia cultivation Vietnam; Brazil; Indonesia; India; Sri Lanka; etc. color black; white; green link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian pepper; black pepper nan 胡椒 hújiāo [barbarian-pepper] bors [pepper] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saffron</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/saffron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/saffron/</guid>
      <description>Saffron#Overview#id saffron species Crocus sativus L. family Iridaceae plant part used stigma (style) region of origin Greece macroarea Med.; W. Asia cultivation Iran; Spain; Kashmir; etc. color deep red; dyes in orange link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan 藏紅花 zànghónghuā [Tibetan-red-flower] nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sichuan Pepper</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/Sichuan_pepper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/Sichuan_pepper/</guid>
      <description>Sichuan Pepper#Overview#id Sichuan pepper species Zanthoxylum bungeanum Maxim. family Rutaceae plant part used pericarp region of origin China macroarea Asia cultivation China color red; green link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan فلفل سيتشوان fulful sītshuwān [Sichuan pepper] 花椒 huā​jiāo [flower-pepper] szecsuáni bors [Sichuan pepper] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Anise</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/star_anise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/star_anise/</guid>
      <description>Star Anise#Overview#id star anise species Illicium verum Hook.f. family Schisandraceae plant part used pericarp region of origin SE. China; Vietnam macroarea Asia cultivation China, Laos, Vietnam, Korea, Japan, Taiwan, Hainan, Philippines (POWO) color orange brown link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan يانسون نجمي yānsūn najmī [star anise] 八角 bājiǎo [octagon] csillagánizs [star-anise] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turmeric</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/turmeric/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/turmeric/</guid>
      <description>Turmeric#Overview#id turmeric species Curcuma longa L. family Zingiberaceae plant part used rhizome region of origin India macroarea Asia cultivation China, Honduras, India, Indonesia, Jamaica color orange-yellow link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan 薑黃 jiānghuáng [ginger-yellow] nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vanilla</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/vanilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/vanilla/</guid>
      <description>Vanilla#Overview#id vanilla species Vanilla planifolia Jacks. ex Andrews family Orchidaceae plant part used fruit region of origin Tropical America macroarea Americas cultivation Madagascar; Indonesia; Mexico; Papua New Guinea; China color dark brown pod; creamy white extract link POWO Names#English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nan nan 香草 xiāngcǎo [fragrant-herb] nan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allspice</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/spices/test/</guid>
      <description>HOW TO:
pandoc -s example4.tex -o example5.mdAllspice#Overview#id allspice species Pimenta dioica (L.) Merr. family Myrtaceae Names#EnglishallspiceArabicفلفل إفرنجيChinese多香果Allspice#::: note Introducing the Spice profile box. As it can be seen above in Spice profile [spice:allspice]{reference-type=&amp;ldquo;ref&amp;rdquo; reference=&amp;ldquo;spice:allspice&amp;rdquo;} presenting allspice, this business-card-like environment gives a quick reference of the spice under scrutiny in a concise way. This is intended to be a convenience for the reader to return and glance back at brief, factual information about a particular item whenever necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/pages/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/pages/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy statement#Traffic on this website is tracked by the creator using Google Analytics out of curiosity of what people click on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/pages/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/pages/terms/</guid>
      <description>Terms &amp;amp; conditions#Right now the website and the database are still under development, use with caution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testpage</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/testpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/testpage/</guid>
      <description>⚓ Website Under Construction ⚓</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/posts/markdown-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/posts/markdown-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following markdown file showcases all the features one can achieve within markdown and with Hugo shortcodes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Template</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/posts/template/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/posts/template/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sources</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/sources/</guid>
      <description>⚓ Website Under Construction ⚓
Sources#Primary Literature#Secondary Literature#Books#Articles#</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cite</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/cite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/cite/</guid>
      <description>How to Cite?#⚓ Website Under Construction ⚓</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/section/first-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/section/first-page/</guid>
      <description>First page#Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.
Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/section/second-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/docs/section/second-page/</guid>
      <description>Second Page#Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat.
Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
