<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Spices &amp; Spice Terminology Database 1.0 (Beta)</title>
    <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Spices &amp; Spice Terminology Database 1.0 (Beta)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://partigabor.github.io/spice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Allspice</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/allspice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/allspice/</guid>
      <description>Allspice#Illustration of Pimenta dioica (L.) Merr. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Allspice (Pimenta dioica (L.) Merr.) is a culinary spice from the Myrtaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of S. Mexico to C. America; Caribbean.2 It is used for its unripe fruit and leaf, primarily for pickles, wines, desserts, liquors. Its aroma is described as pungent, mixed, spicy, with a heat index of 4.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian allspice فلفل إفرنجي 多香果 szegfűbors Overview#id allspice species name Pimenta dioica (L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anise</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/anise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/anise/</guid>
      <description>Anise#Illustration of Pimpinella anisum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Anise (Pimpinella anisum L.) is a culinary spice from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of E. Mediterranean; W. Asia.2 It is used for its fruit and oil, primarily for pastries, candies, liquors. Its aroma is described as licorice-like, sweet, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian anise أنيسون 茴芹 ánizs Overview#id anise species name Pimpinella anisum L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asafoetida</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/asafoetida/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/asafoetida/</guid>
      <description>Asafoetida#Illustration of Ferula foetida (Bunge) Regel from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Asafoetida (Ferula foetida (Bunge) Regel) is a culinary and medicinal spice from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Iran; W. and C. Asia.2 It is used for its gum-resin (latex), primarily for curries; expectorant. Its aroma is described as pungent, rotten, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian asafoetida حلتیت 阿魏 ördöggyökér Overview#id asafoetida species name Ferula foetida (Bunge) Regel family Apiaceae part used gum-resin (latex) macroarea Asia region of origin Iran; W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caraway</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/caraway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/caraway/</guid>
      <description>Caraway#Illustration of Carum carvi L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Caraway (Carum carvi L.) is a culinary spice from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Mediterranean; Eurasia.2 It is used for its fruit, primarily for breads, sausages, cheese; carminative. Its aroma is described as warm, sweet, anise-like, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian caraway كراويا 葛縷子 fűszerkömény Overview#id caraway species name Carum carvi L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardamom</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/cardamom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/cardamom/</guid>
      <description>Cardamom#Illustration of Elettaria cardamomum (L.) Maton from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Cardamom (Elettaria cardamomum (L.) Maton) is a culinary spice from the Zingiberaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of India.2 It is used for its fruit (seed pods, capsules), primarily for desserts, coffees, curries. Its aroma is described as pungent, eucalyptus-like, with a heat index of 2.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian cardamom هال 豆蔻 kardamom Overview#id cardamom species name Elettaria cardamomum (L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cassia</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/cassia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/cassia/</guid>
      <description>Cassia#Illustration of Cinnamomum cassia (L.) J.Presl. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Cassia (Cinnamomum cassia (L.) J.Presl.) is a culinary and medicinal spice from the Lauraceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Southeast China.2 It is used for its bark and fruit, primarily for flavor; diarrhea. Its aroma is described as pungent, cinnamon-like, with a heat index of 3.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian cassia سليخة 肉桂 kasszia(fahéj) Overview#id cassia species name Cinnamomum cassia (L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chile</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/chile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/chile/</guid>
      <description>Chile#Illustration of Capsicum annuum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Chile (Capsicum annuum L.) is a culinary spice from the Solanaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Central America.2 It is used for its fruit, primarily for flavors; analgesic. Its aroma is described as pungent, fiery, with a heat index of 4-10.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian chile فلفل حار 辣椒 paprika Overview#id chile species name Capsicum annuum L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinnamon</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/cinnamon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/cinnamon/</guid>
      <description>Cinnamon#Illustration of Cinnamomum verum J.Presl. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Cinnamon (Cinnamomum verum J.Presl.) is a culinary and medicinal spice from the Lauraceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Sri Lanka; SW. India.2 It is used for its bark and leaf, primarily for flavor; anti-microbial. Its aroma is described as sweet, fragrant, pungent, with a heat index of 3.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian cinnamon قرفة 錫蘭肉桂 fahéj Overview#id cinnamon species name Cinnamomum verum J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clove</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/clove/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/clove/</guid>
      <description>Clove#Illustration of Syzygium aromaticum (L.) Merr. \&amp; L.M.Perry from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Clove (Syzygium aromaticum (L.) Merr. &amp;amp; L.M.Perry) is a culinary and medicinal spice from the Myrtaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Moluccas (Indonesia).2 It is used for its flower buds, primarily for meats, sauces; anesthetic. Its aroma is described as sweet, pungent, astringent, with a heat index of 5.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian clove قرنفل 丁香 szegfűszeg Overview#id clove species name Syzygium aromaticum (L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coriander</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/coriander/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/coriander/</guid>
      <description>Coriander#Illustration of Coriandrum sativum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Coriander (Coriandrum sativum L.) is a culinary spice and herb from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Mediterranean; W. Asia; India; SW As.2 It is used for its fruit and leaf, primarily for curries; anti-microbial. Its aroma is described as warm, aromatic, sweet, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian coriander كزبرة 芫荽 koriander Overview#id coriander species name Coriandrum sativum L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cumin</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/cumin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/cumin/</guid>
      <description>Cumin#Illustration of Cuminum cyminum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Cumin (Cuminum cyminum L.) is a culinary spice from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of W. &amp;amp; C. Asia; India .2 It is used for its fruit, primarily for curries, breads; colic. Its aroma is described as peppery, aromatic, with a heat index of 4.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian cumin كمون 孜然 római kömény Overview#id cumin species name Cuminum cyminum L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dill</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/dill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/dill/</guid>
      <description>Dill#Illustration of Anethum graveolens L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Dill (Anethum graveolens L.) is a culinary spice and herb from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Nort Africa; West Asia.2 It is used for its fruit and leaf, primarily for pickles, fish, breads; gripe. Its aroma is described as bitter-sweet, cool, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian dill شبت 蒔蘿 kapor Overview#id dill species name Anethum graveolens L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fennel</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/fennel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/fennel/</guid>
      <description>Fennel#Illustration of Foeniculum vulgare Mill. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Fennel (Foeniculum vulgare Mill.) is a culinary spice and herb and vegetable from the Apiaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Med.2 It is used for its fruit and leaf, primarily for fish, breads, sausages; colic. Its aroma is described as licorice-like, warm, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian fennel شمر 茴香 édeskömény Overview#id fennel species name Foeniculum vulgare Mill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fenugreek</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/fenugreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/fenugreek/</guid>
      <description>Fenugreek#Illustration of Trigonella foenum-graecum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Fenugreek (Trigonella foenum-graecum L.) is a culinary spice and herb from the Fabaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of S Eur; W As.2 It is used for its seed and leaf, primarily for curries, breads; diabetes. Its aroma is described as like burnt sugar, bitter, with a heat index of 2.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian fenugreek حلبة 胡蘆巴 görögszéna Overview#id fenugreek species name Trigonella foenum-graecum L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginger</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/ginger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/ginger/</guid>
      <description>Ginger#Illustration of Zingiber officinale Roscoe from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Ginger (Zingiber officinale Roscoe) is a culinary and medicinal spice from the Zingiberaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of South East Asia; India (secondary).2 It is used for its rhizome, primarily for Asian cooking; anti-emetic. Its aroma is described as fiery, pungent, with a heat index of 7.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian ginger زنجبيل 薑 gyömbér Overview#id ginger species name Zingiber officinale Roscoe family Zingiberaceae part used rhizome macroarea Asia region of origin South East Asia; India (secondary) cultivation India; Jamaica; Nigeria; Sierra Leone color light yellow when fresh, beige when powdered botanical database POWO Etymologies#English ginger, ca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Pepper</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/long_pepper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/long_pepper/</guid>
      <description>Long Pepper#![Illustration of Piper_longum](/images/kohler/long pepper.png)
Illustration of Piper longum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Long Pepper (Piper longum L.) is a culinary and medicinal spice from the Piperaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of E. Himalaya to S. China; Indo-China.2 It is used for its fruit, primarily for South and Souteast Asian cuisine; Ayurveda and TCM. Its aroma is described as pungent, peppery, with a heat index of 4-9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mace</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/mace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/mace/</guid>
      <description>Mace#Illustration of Myristica fragrans Houtt. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Mace (Myristica fragrans Houtt.) is a culinary spice from the Myristicaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Moluccas (Indonesia).2 It is used for its aril, primarily for confectionary; peptic ulcers. Its aroma is described as sweet, bitter, salty, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian mace بسباسة 肉豆蔻皮 szerecsendió-virág Overview#id mace species name Myristica fragrans Houtt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutmeg</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/nutmeg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/nutmeg/</guid>
      <description>Nutmeg#Illustration of Myristica fragrans Houtt. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Nutmeg (Myristica fragrans Houtt.) is a culinary spice from the Myristicaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Moluccas (Indonesia).2 It is used for its seed, primarily for desserts, eggnog; diahrrhea. Its aroma is described as sweet, warm, nutty, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian nutmeg جوز الطيب 肉豆蔻 szerecsendió Overview#id nutmeg species name Myristica fragrans Houtt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepper</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/pepper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/pepper/</guid>
      <description>Pepper#Illustration of Piper nigrum L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Pepper (Piper nigrum L.) is a culinary and medicinal spice from the Piperaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Malabar coast (South India).2 It is used for its fruit, primarily for flavors; colds. Its aroma is described as pungent, hot, with a heat index of 3-8.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian pepper فلفل 胡椒 bors Overview#id pepper species name Piper nigrum L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saffron</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/saffron/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/saffron/</guid>
      <description>Saffron#Illustration of Crocus sativus L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Saffron (Crocus sativus L.) is a culinary spice and dye from the Iridaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Greece.2 It is used for its stigma (style), primarily for bouillabaise, rice; fevers. Its aroma is described as pungent, bitter, with a heat index of 0.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian saffron زعفران 藏紅花 sáfrány Overview#id saffron species name Crocus sativus L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sichuan Pepper</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/Sichuan_pepper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/Sichuan_pepper/</guid>
      <description>Sichuan Pepper#![Illustration of Zanthoxylum_bungeanum](/images/kohler/Sichuan pepper.png)
Illustration of Zanthoxylum bungeanum Maxim. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Sichuan Pepper (Zanthoxylum bungeanum Maxim.) is a culinary spice from the Rutaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of China.2 It is used for its pericarp, primarily for meats; colic. Its aroma is described as woodsy, peppery, with a heat index of 3.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian Sichuan pepper فلفل سيتشوان 花椒 szecsuáni bors Overview#id Sichuan pepper species name Zanthoxylum bungeanum Maxim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Anise</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/star_anise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/star_anise/</guid>
      <description>Star Anise#![Illustration of Illicium_verum](/images/kohler/star anise.png)
Illustration of Illicium verum Hook.f. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Star Anise (Illicium verum Hook.f.) is a culinary spice from the Schisandraceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of SE. China; Vietnam.2 It is used for its pericarp, primarily for meats, desserts; colic. Its aroma is described as bitter, licorice-like, with a heat index of 3.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian star anise يانسون نجمي 八角 csillagánizs Overview#id star anise species name Illicium verum Hook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turmeric</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/turmeric/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/turmeric/</guid>
      <description>Turmeric#Illustration of Curcuma longa L. from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Turmeric (Curcuma longa L.) is a culinary and medicinal and ritualistic spice and dye from the Zingiberaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of India.2 It is used for its rhizome, primarily for curries, dye; antiseptic. Its aroma is described as warm, acrid, bitter, with a heat index of 3.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian turmeric كركم 薑黃 kurkuma Overview#id turmeric species name Curcuma longa L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vanilla</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/vanilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/spices/vanilla/</guid>
      <description>Vanilla#Illustration of Vanilla planifolia Jacks. ex Andrews from Köhler&#39;s Medizinal-Pflanzen (1887).Vanilla (Vanilla planifolia Jacks. ex Andrews) is a culinary spice from the Orchidaceae family,1 originating in the region(s) of Tropical America.2 It is used for its fruit, primarily for flavouring; baking; desserts; perfumery; aromatherapy. Its aroma is described as fragrant, sweet, delicious, with a heat index of 1.3
English Arabic Chinese Hungarian vanilla فانيليا 香草 vanília Overview#id vanilla species name Vanilla planifolia Jacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search &amp; Index</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can search the website using the &lt;code&gt;search bar&lt;/code&gt; on the left side panel. Alternatively, you can also navigate to various spice pages by selecting related &lt;em&gt;categories&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;tags&lt;/em&gt; visible on the right side panel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide and Hugo Shortcodes</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/meta/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/meta/help/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following markdown file showcases all the features one can achieve within markdown and with Hugo shortcodes, which are featured on this website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/meta/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/meta/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact#gabor.parti@polyu.connect.hk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/meta/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/meta/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy statement#Traffic on this website is tracked by the creator using Google Analytics; out of curiosity of which spices people click on more, and from what countries visitors are from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/meta/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/meta/terms/</guid>
      <description>Terms &amp;amp; conditions#The website and the database are still under development, please use with a grain of salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction## Species English Chinese Translit. Arabic Translit.1 Pimenta dioica allspice 多香果 duōxiāngguǒ فلفل إفرنجي filfil ifranjī2 Pimpinella anisum anise 茴芹 huíqín ينسون yansūn3 Ferula assa-foetida et al. asafoetida 阿魏 wèi حلتیت ḥiltīt4 Carum carvi caraway 葛縷子 gělǚzi كراويا karāwiyā5 Elettaria cardamomum cardamom 荳蔻 dòukòu هال hāl6 Cinnamomum cassia cassia 肉桂 ròuguì سليخة salīkha7 Capsicum annuum et al. chile 辣椒 làjiāo فلفل حار fulful hārr8 Cinnamomum verum cinnamon 錫蘭肉桂 xīlánròuguì قرفة qirfa9 Syzygium aromaticum clove 丁香 dīngxiāng قرنفل qaranful10 Coriandrum sativum coriander 芫荽 yánsui كزبرة kuzbara11 Cuminum cyminum cumin 孜然 zīrán كمون kammūn12 Anethum graveolens dill 蒔蘿 shíluó شبت shibitt13 Foeniculum vulgare fennel 茴香 huíxiāng شمر shamar14 Trigonella foenum-graecum fenugreek 胡蘆巴 húlúbā حلبة ḥulba15 Zingiber officinale ginger 薑 jiāng زنجبيل zanjabīl16 Piper longum long pepper 蓽撥 bìbō دار فلفل dār filfil17 Myristica fragrans mace 肉荳蔻皮 ròudòukòupí بسباسة basbāsa18 Myristica fragrans nutmeg 肉荳蔻 ròudòukòu جوز الطيب jawz al-ṭīb19 Piper nigrum pepper 胡椒 hújiāo فلفل filfil, fulful20 Crocus sativus saffron 番紅花 fānhónghuā زعفران zaʿfarān21 Zanthoxylum spp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Köhler&#39;s Medicinal Plants</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/posts/koehler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/posts/koehler/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Botanical-anatomical illustrations are taken from Köhler&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Medicinal Plants&lt;/em&gt;, published in three volumes between 1887 and 1898. These volumes are in the public domain, and can be accessed online in high definition scans.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Diffusion of Spices</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/diffusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/diffusion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Language of Spices</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/language/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Readings</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/readings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/readings/</guid>
      <description>Sources#Primary Literature#Secondary Literature#Books#Bergreen, 2007
Dalby, 2000
Frankopan, 2012
Hansen, 2012
Krondl, 2007
1 2 3 4 5
Bergreen, L. (2007). Marco Polo: From Venice to Xanadu (1st ed). Alfred A. Knopf. https://www.worldcat.org/title/191923003&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
Dalby, A. (2000). Dangerous Tastes: The Story of Spices. University of California Press. https://www.worldcat.org/title/44979585&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
Frankopan, P. (2012). The Silk Roads: A new history of the world. Bloomsbury. https://www.worldcat.org/title/1200801737&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
Hansen, V.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sources</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/sources/</guid>
      <description>Sources#Primary Literature#Secondary Literature#Books#Articles#</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cite</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/cite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/cite/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Thesis</title>
      <link>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://partigabor.github.io/spice/book/thesis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
